clubxiangqi.com 2012-12-31

# Play Chinese Chess - Xiangqi at Club Xiangqi

Last updated on 03/22/2002 

Privacy Policy

ClubXiangQi.com (CXQ) respects the privacy rights of our online visitors and recognize the importance of protecting the information collected about you. We have adopted an Online Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store and use the information you provide. 

If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding our privacy statement or policies, please contact ClubXiangQi at webmaster@clubxiangqi.com. 

What personal information is collected? 

ClubXiangQi.com only collects personal information from our online visitors on a voluntary basis and only during registration for membership on our sites or when you request services from third party service providers on our site. Information collected may include your name, e-mail address, phone number, home address and birth date. We do not require this information to obtain access our site; however, you will not be able to access areas that require registration. 

Whatever the purpose may be, we will only collect information to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to fulfill your requests and our legitimate business objectives. 

Online Chat Rooms and Profiles 

You may choose to disclose information about yourself in our online chat rooms or in creating user "profiles" when you play games on our sites. Information that you disclose in chat rooms or in "profile" information is public information, and there is no expectation of privacy or confidentiality in either place. Please see our Terms of Service on this point and for other guidelines about posting content on our websites. 

If you are 12 years old and under, please note the following. CXQ encourages parents to spend time online with their children and urges parents to instruct their children to never give out their real names, addresses or phone numbers, without permission, when using the Internet. We recognize a special obligation to protect personal information obtained from young children. Therefore, with respect to children residing in certain jurisdictions, no information should be submitted nor posted to CXQ's online sites by children 12 years of age or under. 

If for any reason you are concerned about your child's personally identifiable, or should you wish to have your child's name removed from our records, please contact us at webmaster@clubxiangqi.com and we will be happy to remove your child's information as appropriate. 

What about cookies? 

Cookies are small files downloaded to your computer to track movements within websites. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interest and for other purposes. For example, some of our sites use "cookies" or other methods to monitor website usage. We may collect information on what games are played, how much time is spent playing the games and which ads or links are clicked. 

We use an outside ad companies to display ads. These ads may contain cookies. Cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. Aggregate consumer data may be shared with the advertising companies. Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies. You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent. However some areas will not function properly if you do so. 

The companies that serve many of the ads that appear on our site, may also collect information regarding your activities online, including the sites you visit. For more information on ad services and how you can opt out of those services, please visit ad service websites. For more information about the practices of some of the other large ad serving companies that may collect information on your use of the site, you may visit AdKnowledge, Avenue A and MediaPlex to view their privacy statements and opt out policies. 

What happens to the information provided? 

ClubXiangQi.com does not disclose any personal information about registered children under 18 years of age to third parties regardless of parental consent, or share or disclose personal information other than as set forth in this policy. 

The personal information you provide will allow us to alert you to new products, features and enhancements; special offers; upgrade opportunities; and contests and events of interest. From time to time, we are approached by companies and organizations that provide products or services that we believe may be of interest to you, and we may provide your personal information to such third parties. We see this as a value-added service helping you to find useful products or services. We strive to limit use of the information you provide to those offers that we think you would appreciate receiving. You may opt out of this service. See the opt out information below. 

We may use survey information in marketing surveys to select and direct advertising that is more likely to be of interest to a particular member. This information may be transmitted to an ad server owned by the advertising company to match members with ads that they are more likely to be interested in. However, we do not disclose any member's personal information to our advertisers without the member's consent. Participation in member surveys is entirely optional. 

We may use your personal information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can consistently improve our sites to better meet our visitors' needs. To enforce legal rights and the law, or when we have reason to believe that the disclosure is necessary to address potential or actual injury or interference with our rights, property, operations, users or others who may be harmed, we may also disclose information to law enforcement, or the appropriate civil authorities. 

Opt-out provision 

When we first collect information about you, we will offer you the opportunity to opt-out of having your personally identifiable information shared with parties outside of ClubXiangQi.com or its subsidiaries (except to the extent required by law, court order, or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority). In addition, if you do not want ClubXiangQi.com to send you e-mail about our products and services, you can opt out at the time of registration or information collection. If, at a later date, you choose to have your name removed from our database, you can do so by sending an e-mail to webmaster@ClubXiangQi.com. 

Safeguarding your personal information 

We will only collect personal information to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to serve our legitimate business purposes, and we will maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the information you have provided. In addition, we will take reasonable steps to assure that third parties to whom we transfer any data will provide sufficient protection of that personal information. 

Review, correction of your information and requesting removal from mailing lists and deactivating your account 

If for any reason you are concerned that the personal information maintained by ClubXiangQi.com is not correct, or should you wish to have your account(s) deactivated or be removed from our mailing lists, please contact us at webmaster@clubxiangqi.com, and we will be happy to review, update or remove information as appropriate. We may still retain your information on our files however, to resolve disputes, enforce our user agreement, and due to technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of our websites. 

By using this site, you signify your assent to the ClubXiangQi.com Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this site. We reserve the right to make changes in this policy at any time. Please check the policy each time you use our website to ensure you are aware of any changes in our privacy practices. Our privacy policy will indicate the date is was last updated. Also, if there is a substantive change in the way that we use your personal information, we will notify you via e-mail of the relevant changes. If you choose to opt-out of our changed practice, our e-mail will contain instructions on how to opt-out. Your continued use of our site will signify your acceptance of the changes to our Online Privacy Policy.
